https://pages.buckner.org/en-us/privacy-policy

Website Privacy Statement
PurposeTo define the policies for the use of and information obtained through the websites for Buckner International, Buckner Adoption and Maternity Services, Inc., Buckner Children and Family Services, Inc., Buckner Retirement Services, Inc. and Buckner Foundation, Inc., hereafter referred to jointly as Buckner.
Use of LinksThroughout our web pages, we provide links to other servers which may contain information of interest to our readers. We take no responsibility for and exercise no control over the organizations, views or accuracy of the information contained on other servers.
Use of Text and ImagesIf you would like to publish information that you find on our website, please send your request to communications@buckner.org.
If you would like Information about using our logo and images, please visit buckner.org/resources or send your request to communications@buckner.org.
Website Privacy PolicyWe have created this statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy.  We do not collect personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us.  Providing such information is strictly voluntary.  This policy is your guide to how we will handle information we learn about you from your visit to our website.
Online Profile Updates and DonationsIf you complete a profile update form and share your personally identifying information, we may use your contact information to send further information about our organization or to contact your when necessary. You may always opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the “Opt-Out” section below.
Sending us an EmailYou also may decide to send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail message containing a question or comment, or by filling out a web form that provides us this information.  We use personally identifying information from email primarily to respond to your requests.  We may forward your email to other employees who are better able to answer your questions.  We may also use your email to contact you in the future about our programs that may of interest.We want to be very clear:  we will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us.  Providing such information is strictly voluntary.  Except as might be required by law, we do not share any information we receive with any outside parties.
Kids and PrivacyTo the extent of our knowledge of a child visiting our site, special rules apply. We do not request personal information about children, such as first and last name or street address and city.
Opt-Out or Change Your Contact InformationOur site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us through a special online form.  You may choose to receive only specific communications or none at all.  You cannot remove yourself from our database, but you can prevent unwanted communication.
Questions about our policiesIf you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at:
Buckner InternationalAttn:  Webmaster700 N Pearl St., Suite 1200Dallas, TX 75201214-758-8000communications@buckner.org
GET UPLIFTING STORIES OF HOW YOU CAN SHINE HOPE IN THE U.S. AND AROUND THE WORLD!
We're excited to share with you all the ways you can shine hope to vulnerable children and families around the world. We invite you to stay connected with us while also growing in your own faith.
Click below to get the latest news, updates and invitations to exclusive events from Buckner. And, we'll send you spiritual encouragement through our weekly Faith Focus devotion. You won't find these stories and resources anywhere else!
Get the Updates
700 North Pearl St.Suite 1200 Dallas TX 752011-800-546-9352
Email
facebook
twitter
instagram
pinterest
youtube
Social Media Guidelines Guías para Redes Sociales de Buckner
